(Howard's Mother(voice):)Why not?
(Howard:)When I go to weddings
it's to scam on chunky bridesmaids.
(Penny:)I don't know
what I would do with a date.
(Leslie:)Oh, all right.
(Leslie:)I understand.
(Howard:)Thanks.
(Leslie:)Hey, I'm really sorry
about that Geneva trip.
- What about it?
- Oh, didn't you hear?
(Leslie:)I had to reduce the number of people going
and you didn't make the cut.
(Howard:)When did that happen?
(Leslie:)About 12 seconds ago.
(Howard:)Hold on. Are you saying if I don't go
to the wedding, I can't go to Geneva?
Well, actually, I'm trying not to say it.
(Howard:)Okay, I'm sorry,
but that makes me a little uncomfortable.
- How so?
- Because it's like you're controlling me...
(Howard:)...with new equipment
and research trips.
If I weren't controlling you with equipment
and trips, I'd be uncomfortable.
- How so?
- Because we'd be in a real relationship...
(Leslie:)...with feelings and all that crap.